wimsbios.com 2015-10-04

# Privacy policy - Wim's BIOS • Wim's BIOS

Wim's BIOS Page, and its advertisers and affiliates are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users.

We collect information from you when you register on our forum, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our forum, you may be asked to enter your e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 'Cookies', which are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

This website uses Google Analytics to help analyse how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity for Wim's BIOS

We will never (and will not allow any third party) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any personally identifiable information of visitors to our site. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Neither we nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any personally identifying information from any source, unless you explicity submit that information via a fill-in form on our website.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. We may release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Wim's BIOS Page does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address, except when you sign up for the forum or other fill-in forms on our site. This information will be explicitly asked and not retrieved in some without you knowing it.

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into the forum at <http://www.wimsbios.com/forum/> and going to the 'User Control Panel'

Our forum is in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act) - if you're under 13 years of age we require a written confirmation (via email) from an adult before your account becomes active.

Wim's BIOS Page uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)

#### 3rd party advertisers

Wim's BIOS Page works with the following 3rd party advertisers that serve ads to this site. 

  * Infolinks is an In Text advertising service which creates links within the Wim's BIOS content. If you hover your mouse over these double underlined links, you will see a small dialog box containing an advertisement related to the text. You can choose to move the mouse away and go on with your browsing, or to click on the box and visit the relevant ad. [Click here to opt-out from Infolinks Double Underline Link Ads](http://www.infolinks.com/learn-more-about-infolinks?pid=34141&wsid=0)
  * To find out more about how InfoLinks manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.infolinks.com/privacy-policy>
  * To find out more about how Google.com manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.google.com/adsense>

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey, the forum or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails. The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
  * Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.wimsbios.com/termsofservice.jsp>

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at:

  * Email: [wb@wimsbios.com](mailto:wb@wimsbios.com)
  * Address: Wim Bervoets - Kaulillerweg 10 - 3990 Grote Brogel - Belgium

## Need help? Ask your question here!

( **Examples:** how to update your BIOS, how to identify your motherboard)
